The rain? No way. This ain't rain.
That's interesting.
It looks like a... oh.
The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
Seize it.
Raise your flag and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand for
the endless everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion I believe,
someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way to the moon's day.
Swaying in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved?
For the horizon on the
other side is, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, is what I am for.
And though I travel far from
where my search began, overseas,
the green end shores of sand, through
the endless everlasting world I've been.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me,
someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I will search for everywhere.
The End
I know!
This is just an awful dream! Yay!
I love dreams!
Heads up!
I don't think the party's over yet!
It won't stop falling!
The rudder!
Turn the rudder!
That'll never work in these waves!
Luffy, you've got to protect the ship!
She's taken a beating!
Right!
Stop!
I cast aside my worries and reach
deep within to find my happy place.
And when I open my eyes, this serene
landscape is all that will lay before me.
A skeleton dead guy!
Throw that nasty thing at me, you idiot!
They're falling everywhere!
I'm surrounded by dead!
What if this stuff's gonna stop falling?
Alright, why did a ship
just fall out of the sky?
Captain Error, the sky's clear, who knows?
I knew coming to the
Grand Line was a mistake!
It freaks me out!
What's wrong, Nami?
Problem?
Oh, no!
The Log Pose is broken!
It's pointing into the sky!
It's not broken.
The Log Pose registers an island
with a strong magnetic pull,
and its needle is reflecting that.
If the needle is pointing toward the sky,
then it must be pointing
toward Sky Island.
Sky Island?
Are you serious?
There's a floating island up there?
If there is one, then it's full of
skeletons and rickety-hole ships!
That's ridiculous.
I don't see anything but sky.
That's not exactly how it works.
It's not an island above us,
but an entire ocean. No way!
I'm still confused.
Yeah!
Raise the sails and set
our course for Sky Island!
Matt, are we ready?
Put the rudder down and point
the bow high into the sky!
Skyward ho!
Did it just hit you?
The fact that, you know,
we can't fly and all that?
To tell you the truth, all I know about
Sky Island is word of mouth. Rumor.
I've never actually seen it.
Of course not, because it's a lie.
Islands don't float in the sky.
Our Log Pose is broken, that's all it is.
Not quite, Ms.
Navigator.
You're trying to fix something
that's not even broken.
We should be trying to find
a way to get to Sky Island.
You really need to learn
to trust your instruments.
No matter how crazy things get or how weird
the situation is we find ourselves in,
never doubt the Log Pose
out here on the water.
This is one of the most
steadfast and unbreakable rules.
What we should be doubting is
the common sense we all have that
tells us an island cannot exist
in the sky on an ocean of nothing.
That needle is pointing toward an island.
I bet my life on it.
That's disgusting, digging
through a dead man's clothes.
That's really going to tell you something?
Don't know.
You're into some pretty
weird stuff, Robin.
Any lady with a fascination for dead
things is interesting in my book.
Where'd Luffy go? Okay. Jump!
What kind of trouble are those
two getting themselves into now?
Probably the bad kind.
Hey, looks good as new.
Except for the holes on the crown.
Those came from an external source.
Oh, yeah.
Looks like it could have been
arrows or a spear or something.
Not quite, but good guess.
These are from a medical
procedure called craterization.
Right, Doctor?
An ancient one.
They cut out a small hole in the skull
to remove a foreign mass like a tumor.
And since it leaves the crater
behind, that's how you get the name.
Knowing how old of a technique this is,
I'd say this man has been
dead at least 200 years.
I can also say with confidence
this man was in his early
30s when he died it must have
been during his voyage that
he finally succumbed to the
illness whatever it was much
more than the rest of his
bones his teeth have remained
in surprisingly good condition
because he rubbed tar on
them it was a common practice
in the south blue to keep out
bacterial infections and
considering the history of that
region i'd suspect that he
was with an exploratory party
here it is the bris
kingdom of the south blue
they launched the saint
bris as a scout ship
208 years ago that's it that's
the ship that fell on us yeah i
recognize that figurehead out
front it's probably sailed the seas
above us unmanned since the captain
and crew died it's amazing what
you can tell from looking at old
bones i'm sure you've heard that
dead men tell no tales right but
everything around them does if
this was a scouting party we
should find evidence of that on the
saint bris yeah except it's sinking
like a stone what are you doing
you won't believe
it i did it i
found the most incredible thing.
A map of the Sky Island?
It's called Skypiea? That's right!
Then it's true, there really
is an island up there!
Yeah!
The island's real!
It's a dream!
Time to journey up the Sky Island!
Hold on, guys.
We don't know how to get there
or if it's even possible.
Not to mention there are a lot of
fake treasure maps in circulation.
No, I mean, sure it's real.
It's got to be because,
well, just because.
But the fact is, that map doesn't
tell us how to find the planet.
Excuse me, do you mind
not punching the ship?
I put a lot of work into that.
That Nami is a vision even when
she's chewing someone's head off.
This guy, Nami, what?
This isn't about me.
It's about reality.
And the reality is that
we know next to nothing.
What we do know is that we can't
defy gravity and sail upwards.
That's impossible.
What we need is more information.
If a big ship like that made it up there,
then the odds are we
can do the same thing.
We just have to find all the
records left on that ship.
I think the ship's at the
bottom of the ocean by now.
If it sunk, we'll salvage it!
Salvage!
We can't do that!
Salvage?
Really?
Yeah, but we couldn't pull
a ship up from the bottom.
I think they'll have to come
up with a more refined plan.
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
This is adventure!
I know I've done more dangerous
things, but I can't remember what...
Nabi, I swear to find you the answers
you seek or I will refuse to return!
I'll hold you to that.
You'll be safe.
Those barrels are my special design.
They've never been busted.
Good luck. Be careful.
We'll be pulling for ya.
Hey, look at that!
This is Chopper here.
Can you guys call off?
This is Luffy and there's a
ton of monsters down here.
We're on a nest of giant sea snakes.
This is Sanji.
Man, they're staring at me.
Keep going!
They'll be fine, Usopp.
Don't worry.
And Chopper, hold that
brake tightly. Right!
I'm so glad they didn't make me go.
Salvage!
Salvage the sea!
What's all that noise?
Salvage the sea, salvage,
salvage the sea, salvage,
salvage the sea, salvage.
Aye aye sir!
Are we on top of the place
where the ships sank?
Aye aye captain sir!
When they say captain
and sir they're talking
about me prepare to
race the ship what lies
on the bottom now belongs to the king of
all salvagers captain
of the marshada pirates
Great a boat of unstable men
led by an unstable monkey hey
what are you guys doing here in
case you didn't know all these
waters belong to me they do
yeah that's right every vessel
that sinks in these parts
automatically becomes mine you're
not trying to take something
that belongs to me are you so
he's going to bring it to the
surface easier for us but not
for the three guys already in
the water we should just keep
our mouth shut and let him do
it stop mumbling and answer
me are you people trying to
yank one of my salvages out
from under me excuse me can i
ask you a question first you've
got questions for me fine sure
whatever ask me anything are
all of you tough good-looking
men gonna salvage that ship
what thank you i see you know
what a real man looks like
what are you talking about you
called us all tough and good
-looking that includes me well
of course stop you're making me
blush this is disturbing so are
you gonna salvage that thing or
Of course!
I'm not the king of all
salvagers for nothing!
If there's a sunken ship before
me, then I'll salvage it.
If it's not sunken, then I'll
sink it and salvage it later!
Now I know how impressed you
are, but we have to save it.
There's salvaging at hand! Loser.
Do you mind if we watch
you, big strong man, work?
Huh?
Don't tell me you've never seen
a professional salvage before.
You just watch us till
your heart's content!
That's that.
Now we just have to wait
and see what happens.
Below, in the water, there's a...
Captain, we have a problem.
What is it?
Something happened to the guys who
went into the water to set the cradle.
Was it one of those sea kings again?
I don't think so.
It looks like someone went to
town on them with their fists.
What?
You mean someone else besides
our guys are down there?
I'm gonna kill them.
You may not get the chance.
Listen up, you!
There's someone else down
there, so be careful! Oh, sure!
You're a moron!
I want all hands setting the cradle
the ship comes up in 20 minutes!
We've got salvaging to do!
Aye, aye, Captain!
Okay, he's waving at us!
Smile and wave back, I guess.
Just act normal!
Oh, help!
Doing my best.
Don't get stage-fried, fellas.
They're observers.
They want to see something new,
so show them how it's done.
If you're still nervous, try
picturing them in their underwear.
Drop the cradle!
Aye, aye!
Keep your eyes peeled for those intruders!
Aye, aye, sir!
These guys really take their
salvaging seriously, don't they?
I think they're showing off because
their captain has a crush on me.
Move it, man!
I want this done fast!
All right, sir!
Oh, my God.
Saru, look.
Cradle set is locked in place.
What was that?
Ah, so why such a big monkey?
There, on the bow of the ship.
Oh, that!
You like?
It's a special prow I designed.
It ain't in our salvage.
Just watch.
You're gonna love this.
Lower the Brook, hunter!
Aye, aye, sir!
Wow, awesome!
Completely amazing! Are you kidding?
Forty meters to the target.
Thirty meters.
Twenty.
Ten.
Brook hunter joint.
Locked.
Excellent!
Now it's time for me to blow!
Wait, there's no way.
He's actually going to use his
breath to bring up that ship?
That's ridiculous!
Is that a bubble?
The body of the ship is off the floor!
All right, howlera!
Aye, aye, sir!
That's hustle, men!
Send more air!
Aye, aye, sir!
Captain, there's a problem
with the underwater crew!
What?
Talk to me!
What's happening down there?
Is it the intruders? Yes, sir!
They're in the ship!
How dare you lay a hand
on my hard-working men?
Intruders!
Uh, you know, we're not going to
take your picture or anything.
You're not?
He was giving us a photo op?
Help us!
Someone please help us!
I'll be right down!
Continue with the
salvaging operation, men!
Aye, sir!
The salvage looks good.
Check it out.
We don't even need the barrels now.
Well, I don't know how they pumped
this much air into a downed ship.
But what I really want
to know is who they are
and why they're trying
to salvage this thing.
I wonder if something bad happened
to Nami and Robin up on the surface.
I've tried calling them,
but they won't respond.
Who do you guys think you are?
Trying to muscle in on my turf?
Nice makeup.
Thanks, I feel it adds a
refined quality to my face.
Oh yeah, certainly adds something.
What the hell are you talking about?
What do you mean?
What he means to say is who are you?
You're right, how rude of me.
Sometimes I get caught up
in the details of life.
It's one of my shortcomings.
Come on, just tell us who you are already.
There's something else down there!
It's huge!
Anybody just want to run?
Yeah, all you guys from the East
Blue have the best sense of humor.
Well, I don't really know about all that.
Nothing compares to a
one-ton gorilla in makeup.
Oh, shut your mouth.
You know I look good.
Does anyone else see the monster the
size of an island in front of us?